It is irrefutable that employees know the difference between right and wrong.
员工都知道是非对错，这一点无可辩驳。
So why don’t more employees intervene when they see someone exhibiting at-risk behavior in the workplace?
那么，看到有人在工作场所做出危险行为时，为什么出面干预的员工并不多呢？
There are a number of factors that influence whether people intervene.
有几个因素会影响人们是否出面干预。
First, they need to be able to see a risky situation beginning to unfold.
首先，他们需要能够察觉到危险情况正开始发生。
Second, the company’s culture needs to make them feel safe to speak up.
其次，公司文化需要让他们觉得可以放心地说出来。
And third, they need to have the communication skills to say something effectively.
第三，他们需要具备相应的沟通技巧，能把意见有效地表达出来。
This is not strictly a workplace problem; it’s a growing problem off the job too.
这并不单单是工作场所的问题；在工作之外，这一问题也日益严重。
Every day people witness things on the street and choose to stand idly by.
人们每天在街上目睹各种事情，却选择袖手旁观。
This is known as the bystander effect—the more people who witness an event, the less likely anyone in that group is to help the victim.
这叫作“旁观者效应”：目睹某一事件的人越多，这群人中任何一个人去帮助受害者的可能性就越小。
The psychology behind this is called diffusion of responsibility.
这背后的心理机制称为“责任分散”。
Basically, the larger the crowd, the more people assume that someone else will take care of it—meaning no one effectively intervenes or acts in a moment of need.
简单来说，人群越大，就有越多的人以为别人会处理这件事，这就意味着，在需要的时候，实际上没有人出面干预或采取行动。
This crowd mentality is strong enough for people to evade their known responsibilities.
这种群体心理的力量足以让人们逃避自己明知应尽的责任。
But it’s not only frontline workers who don’t make safety interventions in the workplace.
但在工作场所，不实施安全干预的并非只有一线工人。
There are also instances where supervisors do not intervene.
也存在主管不出面干预的情况。
When a group of employees sees unsafe behavior not being addressed at a leadership level, it creates the precedent that this is how these situations should be addressed, thus defining the safety culture for everyone.
如果一群员工看到不安全行为在领导层面没有得到处理，这就开了一个先例：这类情况就该这样处理，从而为所有人定下了安全文化的基调。
Despite the fact that workers are encouraged to intervene when they observe unsafe operations, this happens less than half of the time.
尽管工人们受到鼓励，看到不安全的操作时要出面干预，但真正这样做的情况还不到一半。
Fear is the ultimate factor in not intervening.
恐惧是人们不出面干预的根本因素。
There is a fear of penalty, a fear that they’ll have to do more work if they intervene.
人们害怕受罚，害怕一旦出面干预，自己就得多干活。
Unsuccessful attempts in the past are another strong contributing factor to why people don’t intervene—they tend to prefer to defer that action to someone else for all future situations.
过去尝试失败，是人们不出面干预的另一个重要促成因素：今后无论遇到什么情况，他们往往都宁愿让别人去出面。
On many worksites, competent workers must be appointed.
在许多作业现场，都必须指派称职的工人。
Part of their job is to intervene when workers perform a task without the proper equipment or if the conditions are unsafe.
他们的部分职责，就是在工人没有适当的设备就执行任务时，或者在作业条件不安全时出面干预。
Competent workers are also required to stop work from continuing when there’s a danger.
出现危险时，称职的工人还必须阻止作业继续下去。
Supervisors also play a critical role.
主管也发挥着至关重要的作用。
Even if a competent person isn’t required, supervisors need a broad set of skills to not only identify and alleviate workplace hazards but also build a safety climate within their team that supports intervening and open communication among them.
即使不要求配备称职人员，主管也需要具备多方面的技能，不仅能识别并减轻工作场所的危害，还能在团队内部营造一种安全氛围，支持大家出面干预、彼此坦诚沟通。
Beyond competent workers and supervisors, it’s important to teach everyone within the organization that they are obliged to intervene if they witness a possible unsafe act, whether they’re a designated competent person, a supervisor or a frontline worker.
重要的是，不只是称职的工人和主管，组织里的每一个人都要接受教育，明白：如果目睹可能不安全的行为，那么无论自己是指定的称职人员、主管还是一线工人，都有义务出面干预。